Iden: Welcome back, Agent Meeko. The Admiral needs us to extract an Imperial ally on my home world of Vardos. The target is Protectorate Gleb, a local official who once mentored both Agent Hask and myself. I don't know how this connects to Operation: Cinder, but I have to trust the Admiral. Make the jump to Vardos.
Del: That's the **Dauntless**, the ship we rescued on Fondor. Why’s it here?
Hask: Well, it's delivering cargo. It was carrying those satellites. Moff Raythe said they were needed for Operation: Cinder, but he wouldn’t tell us the target.
Iden: Neither would the Admiral. Now I know why.
Officer: The satellites are aligned, sir.
Garrick: Excellent.
Garrick: I did not call for you, Commander Versio.
Iden: Vardos is our target?
Garrick: One of them, yes.
Iden: Why? The entire planet and its people, they're- they're loyal to the Empire!
Garrick: The Emperor commands it. We will purge this planet and others. Fear shall spread, and the galaxy will remember who is in control.
Iden: This is our home!
Garrick: The Empire is our home! And we will do as the Emperor commands.
Iden: I don’t take orders from dead men.
Garrick: You take orders from me!
Garrick: Activate the satellites. Now.
Garrick: Leave for Vardos immediately. Recover Protectorate Gleb. She is your only target. That is all.
Garrick: That. Is. All.
Garrick: Contact Agent Hask on the **Corvus**. Tell him I need to speak to him, immediately.